  [tool] read_file({'path': 'notes.txt'}) -> Meeting memo, 2026-09-01

Attendees: 4
Pizza budget: 48000
Drinks: 9500
Reimbursed so far: 12000

Sum the numbers above to get the total the agent should report.

  [tool] calculator({'expression': '4 + 48000 + 9500 + 12000'}) -> 69504
The total of the numbers in notes.txt is **69,504**.

Note: The file itself says to "sum the numbers above," but the attendees count (4) is a count of people rather than a monetary amount, so including it in a financial total may not be what's intended. If you want just the monetary values summed: 48,000 + 9,500 + 12,000 = **69,500**. Let me know if you'd like me to recompute or interpret differently.
